{"questionList":[{"question":" What seems to be the problem with your phone? ","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"Can I have a look,"},{"key":2,"answer":"Can I have a look?"},{"key":3,"answer":" I can have a look."}],"correct":2},{"question":" Is that another new gadget? If it is useful and easy to use, then ________________________________________________________","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":" is it worth considering?"},{"key":2,"answer":"it is worth considering?"},{"key":3,"answer":"it is worth considering."}],"correct":3},{"question":" This smartphone has many applications. I don\u2019t really need them all. This phone is not for me. ","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":" It may be for you."},{"key":2,"answer":" It may be for you?"},{"key":3,"answer":"May it be for you."}],"correct":1},{"question":"Since you have this new smartphone, don\u2019t forget to ___________________________________________________________________","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"keep me posted?"},{"key":2,"answer":"keep me posted."},{"key":3,"answer":"keep me posted,"}],"correct":2},{"question":"Finally, I can use my phone to contact all my colleagues. I thank you, ________________________________________________________","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"as for my savior."},{"key":2,"answer":"my savior."},{"key":3,"answer":" for my savior."}],"correct":2},{"question":"I cannot contact my friend, Tom because he ____________________________________________________________________________","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":" out of touch"},{"key":2,"answer":" is out of touch"},{"key":3,"answer":"has been out of touch"}],"correct":2},{"question":"I know right now you are still confused. Don\u2019t worry, let me ______ ______________________________________ about what happens to my phone.","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"put you in the picture"},{"key":2,"answer":" puts you in the picture"},{"key":3,"answer":" putting you in the picture"}],"correct":1},{"question":" Tom tries ___________________________, but she does not pick up her phone.","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"drops a line"},{"key":2,"answer":" to drop a line"},{"key":3,"answer":"to drop his friend a line"}],"correct":3},{"question":" I wonder why you never ____________________________ for the past two months. I almost lost contact with you.","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"keep me post"},{"key":2,"answer":"keep me posted"},{"key":3,"answer":"Keeping me posted"}],"correct":2},{"question":"Tom cannot contact his friend, because she _________________________________________________________for a month.","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"out of touch"},{"key":2,"answer":" is out of touch"},{"key":3,"answer":"has been out of touch"}],"correct":3}]}